<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="193" uniqueCount="144"><si><t>id</t></si><si><t>name</t></si><si><t>description</t></si><si><t>label</t></si><si><t>severity</t></si><si><t>reportId</t></si><si><t>versionId</t></si><si><t>reportDetails</t></si><si><t>Elevation of Global admin privilege</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert when a user is added to the global admin role in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Permission</t></si><si><t>Elevation of Exchange admin privilege</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts if a user gets added to the Exchange admin role in the organization.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Unusual volume of file deletion </t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert with a list of users who recently deleted an unusual number of files in SharePoint or OneDrive in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Information governance</t></si><si><t>{"scheduledReportId":0,"reportId":23116,"searchStr":"","sortOptions":{"CreationTime":1},"filterId":0,"easyFilterForServer":null,"unSavedFilterRules":[{"id":305038,"condition":11,"value":"[0]","displayValue":""}],"globalFilters":null,"viewColumns":null,"intelligentFilterStatus":-1,"intelligentFilters":null,"lastFilterConfigurationModifiedTime":"0001-01-01T00:00:00"}</t></si><si><t>Unusual volume of sign Ins blocked by Access Policy</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert if an unusual number of sign-ins blocked due to access policy by comparing the same day in the previous week's blocked sign-ins.</t></si><si><t>Risky sign-ins</t></si><si><t>Creation of external forwarded rule</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts when a new external forwarded email rule is created in Outlook by the users. </t></si><si><t>Threat Management</t></si><si><t>User license changes</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts if any of the Office 365 licenses have been assigned/revoked for a user in the organization.</t></si><si><t>Configuration changes</t></si><si><t>Anonymous link creations</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of new anonymous link created by users in the organization.</t></si><si><t>External sharing</t></si><si><t>Teams private channel creations</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever a private channel is created in Teams.</t></si><si><t>eDiscovery search created</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts when a user created an eDiscovery search or content search in the organization. </t></si><si><t>{"scheduledReportId":0,"reportId":29812,"searchStr":"","sortOptions":{"CreationTime":1},"filterId":0,"easyFilterForServer":[{"id":300016,"condition":11,"value":"[12013,12027]","displayValue":""}],"unSavedFilterRules":null,"globalFilters":null,"viewColumns":null,"intelligentFilterStatus":-1,"intelligentFilters":null,"lastFilterConfigurationModifiedTime":"0001-01-01T00:00:00"}</t></si><si><t>eDiscovery search exported or previewed</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts when a user previewed or exported any of the eDiscovery or content search results. </t></si><si><t>{"scheduledReportId":0,"reportId":29812,"searchStr":"","sortOptions":{"CreationTime":1},"filterId":0,"easyFilterForServer":[{"id":300016,"condition":11,"value":"[12032,12018]","displayValue":""}],"unSavedFilterRules":null,"globalFilters":null,"viewColumns":null,"intelligentFilterStatus":-1,"intelligentFilters":null,"lastFilterConfigurationModifiedTime":"0001-01-01T00:00:00"}</t></si><si><t>Unusual volume of external file sharing</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert with a list of users who recently shared an unusual number of files with any external users. </t></si><si><t>Malware campaign detected after delivery</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of new malware mails delivered to the users. </t></si><si><t>Advanced Threat Protection configuration changes</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert if any of the Advanced Threat Protection configurations have been changed in the organization. </t></si><si><t>High level risky sign ins</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts if a high-level risky sign-in is detected for a user in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Unusual external user file access activity</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert if any unusual volume of file access activity by external users is detected by comparing the same day in the previous weeks' file access activity. </t></si><si><t>Resources accessed using anonymous links</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert having a list of SharePoint or OneDrive files which is more accessed by comparing the previous day's file access activities. It lets you ensure that a file is not shared wrongly on any public site.</t></si><si><t>Directory setting changes</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever a user has changed the directory setting in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Domain changes</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts if any domain settings have been changed in the organization. </t></si><si><t>DLP rule detected mails</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever any mail matches the Data Loss Prevention rule configured in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Traffic monitoring</t></si><si><t>Data Loss Prevention configuration changes</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert whenever a DLP configuration has been changed in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Mail flow configuration changes</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert if any of the mail flow configurations are changed. </t></si><si><t>Unusual volume of admins' login failures</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert whenever an unusual volume of admins’ login failures has been detected when compared to the same day in the previous week's failed logins.</t></si><si><t>Unusual volume of anonymous link creations</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of users who creates an unusual number of anonymous links in SPO or OneDrive in a day. </t></si><si><t>Admin consent to applications</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert having a list of consents given to any applications by the admins in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Elevation of administrative privilege</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts when a user gets added to any of the admin roles in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Admins forced user password reset</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert when an admin forces password reset for a user to avoid any security breach. </t></si><si><t>Anti-phish policy creations and changes</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever an anti-phish policy is created or updated in the organization. </t></si><si><t>ATP default policy changes</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever the Advanced Threat Protection settings for default policy have been changed in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Unlikely travel risk detections</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts if an impossible travel risk is detected for any users in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Sign ins from anonymous IP address</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts when a user sign-in from an anonymous IP address risk is detected in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Unusual anonymous user file activities</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert containing records of anonymous users who have done unusual volume of file activities within short period. </t></si><si><t>MFA disabled users</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever the MFA feature is disabled for a user in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Group owner changes</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert having a list of users who added to or removed from any of the group ownerships in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Admin confirmed user compromised</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever admins confirmed a risky user as compromised in Azure Active Directory. </t></si><si><t>Teams channel ownership changes</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of newly changed ownership in the Teams channels. </t></si><si><t>License assigned to external users</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert listing all the newly assigned Office 365 licenses to external users. </t></si><si><t>Mailbox non-owner access</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert if an unusual number of non-owner access of any mailbox is detected by comparing the same day in the previous week's non-owner access activity. </t></si><si><t>Unusual number of site invitations shared to external users</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert when an unusual number of site invitations shared to external users by comparing the same day in the previous week. </t></si><si><t>Unusual volume of users' daily login failure summary</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">Creates an alert having a list of users whose failed logins increased by comparing the same day in the previous week's failed login activities. </t></si><si><t>Accessed notes in OneNote</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of accessed notes by comparing the previous week's and current week's accessed notes in OneNote. </t></si><si><t>Accessed OneDrive files</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of accessed files by comparing the previous week's and current week's accessed files in OneDrive. </t></si><si><t>Accessed SharePoint files</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert with a list of accessed files by comparing the previous week's and current week's accessed files in SharePoint. </t></si><si><t>SharePoint DLP rule matched documents</t></si><si><t>Creates alerts whenever any of the SharePoint documents match the Data Loss Prevention rule configured in the organization. </t></si><si><t>All failed activities</t></si><si><t>Creates a single alert by comparing the previous and current week's failed activities for every workload.</t></si><si><t>Sign ins based on application</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert by comparing the previous and current week's sign-ins of each application available in the organization. </t></si><si><t>Resolved risky sign-ins of users</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert whenever a user's risky sign-in gets resolved.</t></si><si><t>Re-enabling blocked user accounts</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert whenever an admin enables any of the previously sign-in disabled user accounts in the organization.</t></si><si><t>Blocked user attempted to login</t></si><si><t>When sign-in blocked users try to login, create an alert with a list of all attempted users with their login details such as location, device, etc.</t></si><si><t>{"scheduledReportId":0,"reportId":20301,"searchStr":"","sortOptions":{"createdDateTime":1},"filterId":0,"easyFilterForServer":[{"id":321039,"condition":11,"value":"[\"UserDisabled\"]","displayValue":"[\"UserDisabled\"]"},{"id":321040,"condition":11,"value":"[\"The user account is disabled.\"]","displayValue":"[\"The user account is disabled.\"]"}],"unSavedFilterRules":null,"globalFilters":null,"viewColumns":null,"intelligentFilterStatus":-1,"intelligentFilters":null,"lastFilterConfigurationModifiedTime":"0001-01-01T00:00:00"}</t></si><si><t>(To do) Admin submission result completed</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert if an admin submission result gets completed</t></si><si><t>(To do) Email reported by user as malware or phish</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert when a user reported an email as malware or phish</t></si><si><t>(To do) User restricted from sending email</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert when a user is restricted from sending email due to outbound policy</t></si><si><t>(To do) Malware campaign detected in SPO and OneDrive</t></si><si><t>Creates an alert when a malware is detected in any SPO and OneDrive files</t></si><si><t>policyId</t></si><si><t>type</t></si><si><t>alertRaiseMethod</t></si><si><t>comparison</t></si><si><t>count</t></si><si><t>duration</t></si><si><t>durationUnit</t></si><si><t>groupByAttributes</t></si><si><t>alertCompareToUnit</t></si><si><t>comparedToOperator</t></si><si><t>alertCompareTo</t></si><si><t>UserId</t></si><si><t>ObjectId</t></si><si><t>SourceFileName</t></si><si><t>UserSharedWith</t></si><si><t>Site</t></si><si><t>Workload</t></si><si><t>appDisplayName</t></si><si><t>userPrincipalName</t></si><si><t>BMW</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">GS </t></si></sst>
